cbfsms.com 2008-06-19

# CBFMail.com

**CardBoardFish Privacy Statement**

In this privacy statement, CardBoardFish has disclosed how it uses and treats all data on the following websites:   
**www.cardboardfish.com (CardBoardFish)  
www.cbfsms.com (CBFSMS)  
www.cbfmail.com (CBFMail)  
www.cbfserver.com (CBFServer)  
www.cbfmobile.com (CBFMobile)  
www.free-ringtones-free-logos.com (FRFL)**

You can find contact information for CardBoardFish at the end of this document. Please use it if you are unsure about any of the items contained herein, we will be more than happy to help resolve your query. CardBoardFish is registered with and complies with the Data Protection Act of 1998. 

**Information Collection and Use**

_Information Collection_

CardBoardFish is the sole owner of the information collected on CardBoardFish, CBFMail, CBFSMS, CBFServer, and FRFL. CardBoardFish collects information from our users at several different points on our Web sites. 

Registration

In order to use areas of these Web sites, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to create an account for the user for the service in which the user has expressed interest. To use certain services, mainly for the ones where the user is required to transfer funds to CardBoardFish, registration of personal information for accounts and records purposes and for contacting you incase of a problem may be required. 

_Order/Payment_

We request information from the user on our order/payment forms. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and home address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user. You will be notified if you are agreeing to make a regular payment before you proceed with it – to terminate a regular payment or dispute a payment email support@cbfmail.com or write to Payments Department, CardBoardFish, PO Box 197, Whitstable, CT5 3YB, United Kingdom. You will be billed by either CardBoardFish or the appropriate third party – you will be notified of who will take the payment when it is made. 

_Information Use_

Information obtained by CardBoardFish is solely for accounts and records, and billing purposes, as detailed in our Data Protection Act of 1998 Registration. We reserve the right to use your information to monitor usage of products and services, and to contact you using it when we deem it necessary. Your information is kept private and secure and is not disclosed to third parties other than to perform actions on behalf of CardBoardFish. None of your information will be used for any secondary purposes or for anything not directly related to the reason why you supplied it. As CardBoardFish take such a high standing on the use of personal information, the user is expected to provide information which is accurate. 

_Profile_

CardBoardFish uses cookies and some other devices during your usage of the sites. CardBoardFish does not create a profile of individual users and visitors and does not target users depending on their usage of the site to protect their privacy. Third party advertisers, however, may create a profile of a user to determine what adverts are served to CardBoardFish users and where.

_Cookies_

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Your password is not stored in a cookie; instead the cookie stores the session ID. This is for your own security and privacy, and if users reject the cookie, the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, users may not be able to use registration systems such as CBFMail, or high security processes such as on CBFSMS or FRFL.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. The information stored by our advertisers is in no way linked to your personal information, which is kept completely private and secure at all times. 

_Third Party Advertising_

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by several globally recognised companies, our Web advertising partners. Information about a users visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. You can email support@cbfmail.com, or write to Advertising Department, CardBoardFish, PO Box 197, Whitstable, CT5 3YB, United Kingdom, for more information. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by CardBoardFish, CBFMail, CBFSMS, and CBFServer only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

_Log Files_

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Log files are kept for your security, not to infringe your privacy.   
_  
Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)_

CardBoardFish does not employ "Clear Gifs" to collect information about individual users. Our advertisers may do at any time, but the information will not be linked in any way to personal details stored by CardBoardFish.   
_  
Important information on Mobile Phone Numbers_

In order to use our FREE services FRFL and CBFSMS, you must enter the mobile phone number of the recipient. This number is only stored by CardBoardFish for logging and security reasons and is in no way disclosed to any third party for no other purpose than to send the item you requested to the number you supplied. As stated in our registration for the Data Protection Act of 1998, all information collected is for accounts and records purposes.

**Communications from the Site**

_Special Offers and Updates_

We send all new CBFMail members a welcoming email (depending on the service, sometimes giving account information, general information, or payment details). Established members will occasionally receive information deemed necessary by CardBoardFish for their use of the services. These messages do not infringe the users privacy and are part of the CardBoardFish service. CardBoardFish does not distribute any personal information to third parties.

_Newsletter_

Optional newsletter services may be provided and withdrawn by CardBoardFish at any time. CardBoardFish will not pass on your email address for these optional newsletters to any third parties unless specified on the individual newsletter subscription page. You can add/remove yourself from these optional newsletters at any time. 

_Service Announcements_

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. These messages are not promotional and are always essential to the users use of CardBoardFish products and services. Receiving these messages is part of the CardBoardFish service. 

_Customer Service_

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email, mail, or phone, in accordance with the users wishes. You may be contacted by our Customer Service staff for a period of time after your enquiry to ensure the matter was resolved, or to notify you of developments. You will normally be notified if we intend to notify you further after following up and issue. Instant receipts of email delivery to our support team may also be in force, giving you more information to your email address instantly.

Our Customer Service staff do not have access to critically private information such as your password or PIN number for a specified service. At all stages of the business, user privacy is extremely important, and user information remains protected at all times.   
_  
_**Sharing**

_Legal Disclaimer_

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. We will make every effort to help the Police services with their enquiries if we believe it is in our users interests and to protect the CardBoardFish service. 

_Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_

We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners or advertisers unless deemed specifically necessary. Any information CardBoardFish does store or share is not personally identifiable and CardBoardFish believes there is no infringement of user privacy. 

_Third Party Advertisers_

Advertisers may collect information while you are using CardBoardFish sites about pages you have viewed, and other viewing details. This helps them provide you with different and interesting adverts on every page you see. CardBoardFish does not share additional information with advertisers. 

These are the instances in which we will share users’ personal information:  
Legal requirements and circumstances   
When permission/authorization has been obtained from a user 

_Third Party Intermediaries_

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. We may also need to use other companies to deal with your requests or provide certain services. Other companies on our behalf will provide some services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

_Service Providers_

Third parties, who are providing a product or service on our behalf to the user, are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. Secondary usage is strictly forbidden.

_Business Transitions_

In the event CardBoardFish goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

_Choice/Opt-out_

Any newsletters you subscribe to from CardBoardFish can be opted for or removed from at any time, and will not automatically subscribe you to other newsletters or mailing lists, or third parties. Other services that ask for your email address on CardBoardFish will do so purely for accounts and records, and to contact you personally when necessary. This is part of the CardBoardFish service. In many cases we will not be able to provide you with a product or service without taking contact details for you.   
_  
Links_

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, CardBoardFish, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by these web sites (CardBoardFish). 

_Surveys & Competitions_

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or competitions. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information. Contact information will be used/shared with the competition/survey to notify the winners, and award prizes, or analyse data. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site, as well as by our advertisers. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice, or the survey or competition is entered through an advert provided by a third party advertising company. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

_Tell-A-Friend_

When using some of our products and systems the user will be asked for a referrer. For example, on signing up for the CBFMail system, you can enter the account name of the person who referred you. This information is used by CardBoardFish for monitoring purposes and occasionally to reward those users who attract others to CardBoardFish for their support. 

_Security_

CardBoardFish takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order forms ask users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number, the information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, invisible, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Daily, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, and are protected from intrusion by a state-of-the-art Intrusion Detection System (IDS). 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to support@cbfmail.com. 

**Supplementation of Information**

In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary, sometimes, for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. 

_Credit Check_

CardBoardFish does not perform credit referencing, nor does it offer Credit facilities. All money transfers are made in advance of receiving the goods. However, checks will be made by our authorised third party to authorise transactions on major credit and debit cards if you are making purchases through CardBoardFish. They will obtain "available credit" information from your card issuer and may validate other details for security reasons.  
_  
ID [Address] Verification_

Addresses may be verified via the relevant post office or organisation. This especially applies to credit card transactions. We reserve the right to verify your personal information at any time, and if we find it to be incorrect we will contact you. If we cannot contact you, you are regarded as "Gone Away". This means you have not kept your information held by us accurately and correctly. Your account will be suspended and in extreme cases of none- contact removed entirely to protect the integrity of the information we hold. It is essential that your personal data is correct and up to date at all time.

_Purchasing History_

CardBoardFish reserves the right to keep details of other transactions, or services you have used, when dealing with us. They will not be disclosed to third parties, and used only for accounts and records purposes.  
_  
Enhancement of Marketing Profile_

All our advertising is handled by the named advertising companies, other advertising companies, or companies acting on their behalf. CardBoardFish does not purchase third party information to assist advertising.   
_  
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information_

CardBoardFish requires you to keep your information accurate and correct. If at any time you wish to see the information held about you by CardBoardFish, as specified by the Data Protection Act 1998, you need to contact us and request your account details. A charge deemed by CardBoardFish as “reasonable” will need to be paid before we release the information to cover our administration costs. If any information held by CardBoardFish then you are responsible to ensure it is corrected. You must also ensure the information given to us is accurate and correct at all times. We will amend any information found to be incorrect but any information provided directly by you (i.e. name and address) is your responsibility to maintain. CardBoardFish reserves the right to retain your personal information for as long as is necessary after you request your account closed. However, you will no longer be bound by the terms and conditions of a service once a CardBoardFish representative has confirmed the account closed. You must no longer use this account. 

_Notification of Changes_

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.   
**  
Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

support@cbfmail.com 

CardBoardFish, PO Box 197, Whitstable, CT5 3YB, United Kingdom.

Your query will be dealt with quickly. If sending a letter please include a return address, contact telephone number, and CBFMail account name/alternative email address.

Thank you.
